[
  {
    "no": 1,
    "question": "When you're going out for the whole day, what will you do?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Plan what you will do and when to do it",
        "score": "J"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Just go", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 2,
    "question": "You consider yourself to be",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "A more spontaneous person", "score": "P" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "A more organized person", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 3,
    "question": "If you were a teacher, which course would you prefer to teach?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "A course based on facts", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "A course involving theories", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 4,
    "question": "You usually",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Mix easily with others", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Are more reserved or restrained", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 5,
    "question": "Generally speaking, with whom do you get along better?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Imaginative people", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Practical people", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 6,
    "question": "Do you often let",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Your emotions dominate your reason",
        "score": "F"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Your reason dominate your emotions",
        "score": "T"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 7,
    "question": "In dealing with many things, you would prefer to",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Act according to your whims", "score": "P" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Act according to a plan", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 8,
    "question": "Are you",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Easy to understand", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Difficult to understand", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 9,
    "question": "Following a schedule",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Suits you", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Makes you feel constrained", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 10,
    "question": "When you have a special task, you would like to",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Carefully organize and plan before starting",
        "score": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Figure out what to do as you go along",
        "score": "P"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 11,
    "question": "In most situations, you would choose",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Let things happen naturally", "score": "P" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Follow a schedule", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 12,
    "question": "Most people would say you are a",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Person who values privacy", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Very open and frank person", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 13,
    "question": "You would rather be considered as a",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Practical person", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Resourceful person", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 14,
    "question": "In a large group of people, usually",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "You introduce everyone", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Others introduce you", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 15,
    "question": "Whom would you prefer to be friends with?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Those who often come up with new ideas",
        "score": "N"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Those who are down-to-earth", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 16,
    "question": "You tend to",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Value emotions more than logic", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Value logic more than emotions", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 17,
    "question": "You would prefer to",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Make plans after observing how things develop",
        "score": "P"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Make plans early on", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 18,
    "question": "You like to spend a lot of time",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Alone", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "With others", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 19,
    "question": "Being with many people",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Makes you feel energized", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Often makes you feel exhausted", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 20,
    "question": "You would prefer to",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Arrange appointments and social gatherings well in advance",
        "score": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Be unrestrained and do whatever is fun at the moment",
        "score": "P"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 21,
    "question": "When planning a trip, you prefer to",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Act according to your feelings on the day for most of the time",
        "score": "P"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Know in advance what you will do most of the days",
        "score": "J"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 22,
    "question": "At social gatherings, you",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Sometimes feel depressed", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Often have a great time", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 23,
    "question": "You usually",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Mix easily with others", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Tend to keep to yourself", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 24,
    "question": "Which type of people attracts you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Those who are quick-witted and very intelligent",
        "score": "N"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Those who are practical and have a wealth of common sense",
        "score": "S"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 25,
    "question": "In your daily work, you would",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Quite enjoy dealing with emergencies that force you to work against the clock",
        "score": "P"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Usually plan in advance to avoid working under pressure",
        "score": "J"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 26,
    "question": "You think others generally",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Take a long time to get to know you",
        "score": "I"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Get to know you in a short time", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 27,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Value privacy", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Be open and frank", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 28,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Pre-arranged", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Unplanned", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 29,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Abstract", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Concrete", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 30,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Gentle", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Firm", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 31,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Think", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Feel", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 32,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Facts", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Ideas", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 33,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Impulsive", "score": "P" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Decisive", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 34,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Enthusiastic", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Quiet", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 35,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Quiet", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Outgoing", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 36,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Systematic", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Random", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 37,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Theory", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Certainty", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 38,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Sensitive", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Fair", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 39,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Convincing", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Touching", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 40,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Statement", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Concept", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 41,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Unrestrained", "score": "P" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Pre-arranged", "score": "J" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 42,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Reserved", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Talkative", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 43,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Methodical", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Unconcerned with details", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 44,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Ideas", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Facts", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 45,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Compassion", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Foresight", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 46,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Benefit", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Blessing", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 47,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Practical", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Theoretical", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 48,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Few friends", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Many friends", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 49,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Systematic", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Impromptu", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 50,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Imaginative", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Matter-of-fact", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 51,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Affectionately", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Objectively", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 52,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Objectively", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Passionately", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 53,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Build", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Invent", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 54,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Quiet", "score": "I" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Sociable", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 55,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Theory", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Fact", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 56,
    "question": "In each of the following pairs of words, which one appeals to you more? Carefully consider the meanings of these words and do not be influenced by their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Sympathetic", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Logical", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 57,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more? Please carefully consider the meanings of the words and disregard their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Analytical", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Sentimental", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 58,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more? Please carefully consider the meanings of the words and disregard their shapes or pronunciations.",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Reasonable", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Fascinating", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 59,
    "question": "When you have to complete a big project within a week, what will you do at the beginning?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "List the different tasks to be done in order",
        "score": "J"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Start working immediately", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 60,
    "question": "In social situations, you often feel",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "It's hard to start a conversation and keep it going with some people",
        "score": "I"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "You can have a relaxed long conversation with most people",
        "score": "E"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 61,
    "question": "When doing something that many people also do, you prefer",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "To do it according to the generally recognized method",
        "score": "S"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "To come up with your own idea", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 62,
    "question": "Can your newly - met friends tell your interests?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Right away", "score": "E" },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Only after they truly get to know you",
        "score": "I"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 63,
    "question": "The subjects you usually prefer are",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Those that teach concepts and principles",
        "score": "N"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Those that teach facts and data", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 64,
    "question": "Which is a higher compliment or praise?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "A consistently emotional person",
        "score": "F"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "A consistently rational person", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 65,
    "question": "You think following a schedule",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Is sometimes necessary, but generally you don't like to do it that way",
        "score": "P"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Is helpful in most cases and is something you like to do",
        "score": "J"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 66,
    "question": "When you are with a group of people, you usually choose",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "To talk with a few individuals you are very familiar with",
        "score": "I"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "To participate in the group conversation",
        "score": "E"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 67,
    "question": "At social gatherings, you will",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Be the one who talks a lot", "score": "E" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Let others talk more", "score": "I" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 68,
    "question": "The idea of making a list of things to be done during the weekend",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Appeals to you", "score": "J" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Makes you lose motivation", "score": "P" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 69,
    "question": "Which is a higher compliment or praise?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Competent", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Compassionate", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 70,
    "question": "You usually prefer",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "To arrange your social appointments in advance",
        "score": "J"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "To do things as the mood strikes you",
        "score": "P"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 71,
    "question": "Generally speaking, when doing a big assignment, you will choose",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "To figure out what to do as you go along",
        "score": "P"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "To first break the work down into steps",
        "score": "J"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 72,
    "question": "Can you talk endlessly with others?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Only with people who share your interests",
        "score": "I"
      },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "With almost anyone", "score": "E" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 73,
    "question": "You will",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Follow some proven effective methods",
        "score": "S"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Analyze the data to see what other methods are available",
        "score": "N"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 74,
    "question": "When reading for fun, you will",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Like unique or innovative ways of expression",
        "score": "N"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Like the author to speak plainly",
        "score": "S"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 75,
    "question": "You would rather work for which type of boss (or teacher)?",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "One who is kind - hearted but often inconsistent",
        "score": "F"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "One who is sharp - tongued but always logical",
        "score": "T"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 76,
    "question": "Most of the time, you do things",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "According to your mood of the day",
        "score": "P"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "According to a pre - planned schedule",
        "score": "J"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 77,
    "question": "Are you",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Able to talk comfortably with anyone as needed",
        "score": "E"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Only able to speak freely with certain people or in certain situations",
        "score": "I"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 78,
    "question": "When making a decision, you think what is more important is",
    "answerOptions": [
      {
        "type": "A",
        "answer": "Weighing according to the facts",
        "score": "T"
      },
      {
        "type": "B",
        "answer": "Considering others' feelings and opinions",
        "score": "F"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 79,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Imaginative", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Real", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 80,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Benevolent and generous", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Determined", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 81,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Fair", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Caring", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 82,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Making", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Designing", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 83,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Possibility", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Certainty", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 84,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Gentleness", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Strength", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 85,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Practical", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Sentimental", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 86,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Manufacturing", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Creating", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 87,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Novel", "score": "N" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Known", "score": "S" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 88,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Sympathy", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Analysis", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 89,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Assertive", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Gentle and caring", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 90,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Concrete", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Abstract", "score": "N" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 91,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Devotedly", "score": "F" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Determinedly", "score": "T" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 92,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Competent", "score": "T" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Kind - hearted", "score": "F" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "no": 93,
    "question": "For each of the following pairs of words, which word appeals to you more?",
    "answerOptions": [
      { "type": "A", "answer": "Practical", "score": "S" },
      { "type": "B", "answer": "Innovative", "score": "N" }
    ]
  }
]
